Guide to the Yale-China Association Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records, 1906-1989; Accession 1991-A-035
  - Hong Kong/Yale China Correspondence, 1/1979-6/1979, 7/1979-7/1980 (Box 28, Folder 385-386)
  - Hong Kong, University of (British), undated (Box 28, Folder 387)
  - Hopkins, Arthur H., Jr. (Former Bachelor 1941-1943), 4/22/1984-4/7/1988 (Box 28, Folder 388)
  - Horowitz, William (Former Trustee), 6/12/1974-7/18/1984 (Box 28, Folder 389)
  - Host Family Program, Yale-China International Center, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 390)
  - How H Works (Made For Steering Committee Meeting), 12/11/1971 (Box 28, Folder 391)
  - HNMC Fellows: Li Xue-Yuan, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 392)
  - HNMC Fellows: Li Xue-Zheng, 7/16/1982-10/10/1983 (Box 28, Folder 393)
  - Hsiang-Ya (Yale in China Med. College: Dr. Phillips, F. Greene Memorial Fund, List of Contributors to and other Info), undated (Box 28, Folder 394)
  - Hsiang-Ya: Journals, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 395)
  - Hsiang-Ya: Journal Contracts, 5/12/1976-6/17/1980 (Box 29, Folder 396)
  - Hsiang-Ya: Journal, 12/2/1976-6/12/1978 (Box 29, Folder 397)
  - Hsiang-Ya: Journal Flyer, 2/8/1977-5/3/1977 (Box 29, Folder 398)
  - Hsiang-Ya: Journal Reviews, 2/1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 399)
  - Huangs Yang-Chih (Stanley) Scholarship Loan Payments, 1974-1977 (Box 29, Folder 400)
  - Hume, Edward, MD, After 1919 (Box 29, Folder 401)
    Notes for Speech: "Doctors East, Doctors West: An American Physician's Life in China"
  - Hume Memorial Library, 2/26/1975 (Box 29, Folder 402)
  - Cao Meihong Hunan Medical College Fellow, 7/14/1982-12/5/1983 (Box 29, Folder 403)
  - Huang Guauxue Hunan Medical College Fellow, 6/22/1982-9/23/1983 (Box 29, Folder 404)
  - Hutchins, Francis (Trustee), Prior 7/1980 (Box 29, Folder 405)
  - Hutchins, Francis S., Dr (Honorary), 4/19/1978-12/4/1988 (Box 29, Folder 406)
  - "I", 2/3/1965-3/8/1977 (Box 29, Folder 407)
  - Imperial China Photography Exhibit, 3/15/1979 (Box 29, Folder 408)
  - Ingholt, Harrold and Janet, 3/29/1982-1/22/1986 (Box 29, Folder 409)
  - Institute of International Relations, Taipei (Tsai Wei-Ping), 7/8/1975-3/9/1976 (Box 30, Folder 410)
  - Internal Revenue Service Tax Exemption Data State # E-01614, 10/11/1939-6/30/1978 (Box 30, Folder 411)
  - "J", 12/28/1973-1/25/1978 (Box 30, Folder 412)
  - "K", 9/13/1972-2/9/1979 (Box 30, Folder 413)
  - Kitchen, Beatrice, Mrs., 4/16/1975-2/6/1989 (Box 30, Folder 414)
  - Kitchen, William, 9/30/1971-11/22/1977, 3/12/1973-1/20/1976, 10/1974 (Box 30, Folder 415-417)
  - Kueh, Y. Y. (Univ. Coordinator) Correspondence, 9/5/1974-12/6/1977 (Box 30, Folder 418)
  - Kwau, T. W. Scholarship Recipient, 1977-1979 (Box 30, Folder 419)
  - "L", 9/26/1972-5/9/1979 (Box 30, Folder 420)
  - Lai, Shu Tong: Overseas Scholar, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 421)
  - Lay, W. P. Faculty Fellow, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 422)
  - Leavens Dickson H: Correspondence, 4/1/1931-7/17/1933 (Box 30, Folder 423)
  - Leavens, Dickson H.: Notes (?), 10/10/1944 (Box 30, Folder 424)
  - Leavens, Dickson and Marjorie: Correspondence and News Clippings, 2/23/1929-3/2/1955 (Box 30, Folder 425)
  - Leavens, Mrs. Dickson H., 9/19/1963-5/2/1972 (Box 30, Folder 426)
  - Leavens, Marjorie, 6/17/1956-10/10/1973 (Box 30, Folder 427)
  - Lee, Sik-Yun: Overseas Scholar, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 428)
  - Lee, Tien Ming: Overseas Scholar, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 429)
  - Leung, Felix (Yale Medical School) Summer Travel Fellowship, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 430)
  - Levenberg, Nancy (Former Staff), 2/22/1979-11/8/1983 (Box 31, Folder 431)
  - Li Chen-Nan (Y-in-C B.S. 21), 7/24/1963-7/6/1973 (Box 31, Folder 432)
  - Li, Chien-Pien, M.D., 11/26/1973-3/15/1982 (Box 31, Folder 433)
  - Lingnan, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 434)
  - Lingnan college, 4/17/1974-5/18/1976 (Box 31, Folder 435)
  - Lingnan Board of Trustees: Correspondence, 6/1974-7/1975, 8/1975-6/30/1976 (Box 31, Folder 436-437)
  - Lingnan Board of Trustees, Annual Meeting, 6/1976 (Box 31, Folder 438)
  - Lingnan Board of Trustees: Correspondence, 7/1/1976-1978 (Box 31, Folder 439-440)
  - Lingnan Meetings, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 441)
  - Lingnan Teaching Program: Lanzhou Blatchford Correspondence, 8/1979-4/1980, 5/1980-7/1981 (Box 32, Folder 442-443)
  - Liu, James T. C. (1970, Princeton E. Asian Studies-Proposed Project For Y in C To Pursue), 2/17/1970-7/14/1970 (Box 32, Folder 444)
  - Local Programs: Bay Area Yale Club, 1/1984 (Box 32, Folder 445)
  - Local Programs: Bergen Co, Yale Club, 2/2/1984 (Box 32, Folder 446)
  - Local Programs: "Books Sandwiched In", 9/30/1982 (Box 32, Folder 447)
  - Local Programs: Boston Area Members Reception, 12/01/1983 (Box 32, Folder 448)
  - Local Programs: Chinese Festivals Slide Show, 2/1/1984 (Box 32, Folder 449)
  - Local Programs: Class of 1957, New York, 4/1984 (Box 32, Folder 450)
  - Local Programs: Conn. International Trade Association, Hartford, 12/8/1983 (Box 32, Folder 451)
  - Local Programs: Lecture for Dartmouth College International Students Association, 4/1983 (Box 32, Folder 452)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Ashland, Oregon, 10/15-11/2/1984 (Box 32, Folder 453)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Asia Society, NYC, 6/21-8/26/1984 (Box 32, Folder 454)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Atlanta, Georgia, 10/1983 (Box 32, Folder 455)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Background, 1978-1987 (Box 32, Folder 456)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Boulder, CO, 4/1-4/23/1984 (Box 33, Folder 457)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Choate, 9/1982 (Box 33, Folder 458)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Colorado Springs CO, 1-2/1984 (Box 33, Folder 459)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Greenwich, CT, 4/1983-5/1983 (Box 33, Folder 460)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Grinnell College, 11/1983 (Box 33, Folder 461)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Kauffman Galleries, Houston TX, 9/13-9/20/1984 (Box 33, Folder 462)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Las Vegas, Nev., 5/11-5/31/1984 (Box 33, Folder 463)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China New Haven, CT, 2/3/1981-10/1/1982 (Box 33, Folder 464)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Westbrook College, 2/1983 (Box 33, Folder 465)
  - Local Programs: Faces of China Winsted, CT, 1/1985-3/1985 (Box 33, Folder 466)
  - Local Programs: Feature Film Series, Spring 1984 (Box 33, Folder 467)
  - Local Programs: Greenwich Field Club, 12/7/1983 (Box 33, Folder 468)
  - Local Programs: Hollywood China, 3/1983-4/1983 (Box 33, Folder 469)
  - Local Programs: "Mao to Mozart" New Canaan, CT, 10/29/1982 (Box 33, Folder 470)
  - Local Programs: NCAAVW, 3/14/1985 (Box 33, Folder 471)
  - Local Programs: NCCS Course, 3/1983 (Box 33, Folder 472)
  - Local Programs: NCCS Course, 2/1984-3/1984 (Box 33, Folder 473)
  - Local Programs: NCCS Course, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 474)
  - Local Programs: PRC Government Officials Visit to Plum Blossoms, 4/1985 (Box 33, Folder 475)
  - Local Programs: Yale Club of Central N.C., 11/4/1984 (Box 33, Folder 476)
  - Loh, Albert (Graduate Applicant from New Asia College Physics), 1966 (Box 33, Folder 477)
  - Long, Charles H., Jr.: Letters And Reports, 9/30/1955-12/31/1956 (Box 33, Folder 478)
  - Lovett: Biographical Information and Pictures, 1/15/1964-9/6/1978 (Box 33, Folder 479)
  - Lovett, Sidney: Memorial, 4/12/1979-4/18/1979 (Box 33, Folder 480)
  - Lovett, Sidney: Trustee Honorary, 3/11/1965-11/27/1979 (Box 33, Folder 481)
  - Luk, Kwok-Sun, Scholar-History, 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 482)
  - "M", 12/28/1971-3/20/1979 (Box 34, Folder 483)
  - Mailing List: Changes: Non Contributors, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 484)
  - Mailing List: Changes: Contributors, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 485)
  - Mailing List: Computer Corrections: Non Contributors, 6/28/1974-7/24/1975 (Box 34, Folder 486)
  - Mailing List: Changes, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 487)
  - Mailing List: Changes: Contributors, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 488)
  - Mailing List: New Haven Contributors, April 1975 (Box 34, Folder 489)
  - Mailing List: Computer Revision, undated (Box 34, Folder 490)
  - Lists of Mail Sent Out Checked by E. Moultry, 11/1971-2/14/1974 (Box 34, Folder 491)
  - Mali, Henry J., 2/6/1974-4/24/1986 (Box 34, Folder 492)
  - McClellan, Edwin (Honorary), 5/6/1980-6/9/1982 (Box 34, Folder 493)
  - McLennan, Donald R., Jr., 3/8/1982-6/6/1985 (Box 34, Folder 494)
  - Medical Committee, 4/16/1959-12/22/1975, 9/25/1972-10/22/1982, 7/12/1977-3/10/1978, 10/6/1978-3/9/1979, 8/8/1979-6/24/1980, 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 495-501)
  - Medical Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 502)
  - Medical Committee Public Program, 5/5/1983 (Box 35, Folder 503)
  - Medical Delegation, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 504)
  - Medical Exchanges: I. Willard Abraham, 11/25/1981, 11/28/1988 (Box 35, Folder 505)
  - Medical Exchanges: Chen Dixia, 8/20/1984, 3/12/1985 (Box 35, Folder 506)
  - Medical Exchanges: Mildred Gordon, 7/2/1974, 11/1986 (Box 35, Folder 507)
  - Medical Exchanges: James L. Hadler, 6/21/1981, 5/31/1985 (Box 35, Folder 508)
  - Medical Exchanges: Gail Henderson, 4/3/1984, 2/27/1985 (Box 35, Folder 509)
  - Medical Exchanges: Hubei Medical Cellege, 1978-1982 (Box 35, Folder 510-512)
  - Medical Exchanges: Hubei Medical College, 1982-1983, undated (Box 36, Folder 513-514)
  - Medical Exchanges: Hunan Medical College, 1979, 10/1/1979, 1980-1982, 10/16/1981-7/1/1982 (Box 36, Folder 515-519)
  - Medical Exchanges: Hunan Medical College Zhau Yue (Fellow), 4/19/1982, 8/10/1983 (Box 36, Folder 520)
  - Medical Exchanges: Hunan Medical College, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 521-522)
  - Medical Exchanges: Hunan Medical College Liu Yongmo (Fellow), 12/19/1981-1986 (Box 36, Folder 523)
  - Medical Exchanges: Fred Kantor, 7/6/1981-11/1913/1989 (Box 36, Folder 524)
  - Medical Exchanges: Katherine Lao, 6/16/1981-2/2/1989 (Box 36, Folder 525)
  - Medical Exchanges: Bernard Lytton, 1/28/1983-9/1918/1984 (Box 36, Folder 526)
  - Medical Exchanges: Sun Ming, 4/8/1985-3/30/1986 (Box 36, Folder 527)
  - Medical Exchanges: Miscellany, 1975, 1979-1980, 10/19/1986, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 528-529)
  - Medical Exchanges: Miscellany (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 36, Folder 530)
  - Medical Exchanges: Miscellany (2 of 2), 8/1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 531)
  - Medical Exchanges: Miscellany, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 532)
  - Medical Exchanges: Miscellany (Addenda), 1981-1982, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 533-534)
  - Medical Exchanges: Miscellany, 1982-1985, 7/19/1985-7/1986 (Box 37, Folder 535-538)
  - Medical Exchanges: Sun Peiwu, 1/7/1981-5/20/1982 (Box 37, Folder 539)
  - Medical Exchanges: Poll and Black, 5/20/1981-6/4/1990 (Box 37, Folder 540)
  - Medical Exchanges: David Young, 2/1/1983-6/15/1984 (Box 37, Folder 541)
  - Medical Exchanges: Robert K. Yu, 7/10/1980-9/1920/1984 (Box 37, Folder 542)
  - Medical Exchanges: Chen Yuanjia, 10/8/1984-11/15/1984 (Box 38, Folder 543)
  - Medical Exchanges: Zhang Zheng, 1/27/1981, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 544)
  - Medical Exchanges: Ling Zhusan, 8/21/1984-11/6/1985 (Box 38, Folder 545)
  - Medical Exchanges: Study Delegation Visit One, 1/17/1979-3/1980 (Box 38, Folder 546)
  - Medical Exchanges: Study Delegation Visit Two, 4/1980-2/1981 (Box 38, Folder 547)
  - Medical Exchanges: Study Delegation Visit Three, undated (Box 38, Folder 548)
  - Medical Seminar: Association of Yale Alumni, 1/1929/1974-5/28/1974 (Box 38, Folder 549)
  - Membership Profiles, 3/3/1982-10/6/1982 (Box 38, Folder 550)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 8/28/1973-3/25/1985, 1981-3/15/1982, 1/5/1981-12/28/1981, 3/16/1982-6/29/1982 (Box 38, Folder 551-554)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982, 1983, 6/17/1982-12/18/1984, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 555-558)
  - The Missions Code, undated (Box 39, Folder 559)
  - Milton Bus Trip, 4/23/1979 (Box 39, Folder 560)
  - Mu, Chien: Letter on 30th Anniversary of New Asia College, undated (Box 39, Folder 561)
  - Musical Instrument Demonstration, 1/7/1980-2/5/1980 (Box 39, Folder 562)
  - John Musser, 10/11/1961-8/3/1990 (Box 39, Folder 563)
  - "N", 2/23/1973-3/1923/1978 (Box 39, Folder 564)
  - Name Change Poll, 3/1975 (Box 39, Folder 565)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: Annual Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 566)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: Correspondence, 1976-1978, 1/1975-1/1976, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 567-569)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: Notes, 3/1973, 1/1973-1/1974, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 570-572)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: Board of Directors Meeting, 10/7/1976, 1/27/1977 (Box 40, Folder 573-574)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: Board Meeting, 6/1977 (Box 40, Folder 575)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: 27th Meeting of the Board of Directors, 10/1928/1975 (Box 40, Folder 576)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: Board of Directors Meeting, 5/21/1975 (Box 40, Folder 577)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: 26th Meeting of the Board of Directors, 4/11/1975 (Box 40, Folder 578)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: 25th Meeting of the Board of Directors, 11/4/1974 (Box 40, Folder 579)
  - National Committee on US-China Relations: 24th Meeting of the Board of Directors, 6/4/1974 (Box 41, Folder 580)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ: China Program, 8/1974-5/28/1976, 6/1976 (Box 41, Folder 581-582)
  - Newsletter: Special Mailing to Large Contributors, 2/23/1973-3/2/1973 (Box 41, Folder 583)
  - New Asia College, 5/1956-1/11/1960 (Box 41, Folder 584)
  - New Asia College Acting President Dr. Y.T. Shen, 6/30/1969-3/4/1970 (Box 41, Folder 585)
  - New Asia College Acting Rep. Wang Chi, 5/14/1968-10/5/1977 (Box 41, Folder 586)
  - New Asia College Board of Governors Tsu-Fa Lee, 2/25/1976-8/5/1977 (Box 41, Folder 587)
  - New Asia College Development Fund: Hong Kong Contributors, 4/19/1973-9/10/1973 (Box 41, Folder 588)
  - New Asia College Faculty Recruitment, 10/14/1971-2/14/1973 (Box 41, Folder 589)
  - New Asia College Junior Staff Quarters, 5/8/1962-9/17/1974, 9/28/1973-12/1925/1976 (Box 41, Folder 590-591)
  - New Asia College President Y. P. Mei, 2/17/1971-8/23/1972 (Box 41, Folder 592)
  - New Asia College Presidents and Heads, 12/15/1971-9/1921/1977 (Box 41, Folder 593)
  - New Asia College: Prior to 1/1979, 3/18/1976-12/13/1978 (Box 41, Folder 594)
  - New Asia College: Teaching Post Notices, 12/14/1973-8/1961 (Box 41, Folder 595)
  - New Asia College: Terms of Service for Faculty, 11/17/1970 (Box 41, Folder 596)
  - "New Asia Life:" Monthly Periodical of New Asia College, 10/15/1978-11/15/1979, 9/28/1979-6/15/1980 (Box 42, Folder 597-598)
  - New Haven Committee, 4/4/1975-9/11/1979 (Box 42, Folder 599)
  - New Haven Committee Mrs G. Harold Welch, Chair, 6/20/1975-6/3/1977 (Box 42, Folder 600)
  - New Haven Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 601-602)
  - New Haven Committee: Chinese Cooking Classes, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 603)
  - New Haven Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 42, Folder 604-605)
  - New Haven Program: Calligraphy Exhibition, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 606)
  - New Haven Program: Lecture Series, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 607)
  - New Haven Programs: 17th Century Chinese Art Exhibit, 12/4/1975 (Box 42, Folder 608)
  - N. G. Big Wan: Scholar (Fine Arts), 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 609)
  - Ng, Lee Ming: Faculty Fellowship, Divinity School, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 610)
  - Nominating Committee, 6/4/1971-7/18/1977 (Box 43, Folder 611)
  - "O", 7/6/1972-5/2/1979 (Box 43, Folder 612)
  - Opera Reception, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 613)
  - "Opium Wars", 2/1979-5/1979 (Box 43, Folder 614)
  - Orientation, 9/1983 (Box 43, Folder 615)
  - Overseas Scholarships: Terms and Arrangements, 6/26/1972-7/28/1972 (Box 43, Folder 616)
  - "P", 7/14/1972-5/8/1979 (Box 43, Folder 617)
  - Panel Speakers, 6/71-3/27/1974 (Box 43, Folder 618)
  - Parsons, John C. (Former Trustee), 10/19/1973-3/9/1979 (Box 43, Folder 619)
  - Peking Opera, 9/23/1981-10/21/1981 (Box 43, Folder 620)
  - Peoples Republic of China: Contacts Before Recognition, 7/31/1973-10/19/1973 (Box 43, Folder 621)
  - PRC Exchanges: And Yin C. Scholarships, 7/27/1972-7/15/1980 (Box 43, Folder 622)
  - PRC Exchanges: Chien Muzhu, 6/30/1982-10/18/1984 (Box 43, Folder 623)
  - PRC Exchanges: Hao Cheng Fu, 3/28/1983-1/7/1984 (Box 43, Folder 624)
  - PRC Exchanges: Huazhong Normal, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 625)
  - PRC Exchanges Huazhong Normal University, 1980-1984 (Box 43, Folder 626-627)
  - PRC Exchanges: Kiang Wehan, 1980-9/27/1983 (Box 43, Folder 628)
  - PRC Exchanges: King Lui Uw, 9/8/1980-6/1982 (Box 43, Folder 629)
  - PRC Exchanges: Li Aizhu, 5/7/1981-12/18/1984 (Box 44, Folder 630)
  - PRC Exchanges: Li Fuing, 3/5/1980-2/10/1986 (Box 44, Folder 631)
  - PRC Exchanges: Miscellany, 9/11/1980-1982, 1979-1980, 5/1979-2/15/1983, 1982-1985, 9/9/1985-4/21/1986 (Box 44, Folder 632-638)
  - PRC Exchanges: Wang Ning, 2/4/1986-9/17/1986 (Box 45, Folder 639)
  - PRC Exchanges: Yuanmov, Nina, 4/18/1983-9/10/1984 (Box 45, Folder 640)
  - PRC Exchanges Wuhan University, 11/1973-1980, 1981-7/1983, 1/1982-4/5/1984 (Box 45, Folder 641-643)
  - PRC Institutions: HNMC, 1984-1985 (Box 45, Folder 644)
  - PRC Institutions: Huazhong, 1984-1985, 6/21/1985-6/16/1986 (Box 45, Folder 645-646)
  - PRC Institutions: Hunan Medical School, 8/1/1985-6/16/1986 (Box 45, Folder 647)
  - PRC Institutions: Yali Middle School, 6/23/1985-10/2/1986 (Box 45, Folder 648)
  - PRC Scholars: Zhou Nan, 7/26/1983-3/16/1984 (Box 45, Folder 649)
  - PRC Wuhan University, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 650)
  - Performing Arts Ensemble, 5/1/1978-7/7/1978 (Box 46, Folder 651)
  - Personnel: Agency Accounts, 8/25/1973-7/2/1977 (Box 46, Folder 652)
  - Personnel: Berman, Jonathan, 9/2/1986-4/6/1988 (Box 46, Folder 653)
  - Personnel: Cady, Janet A., 4/5/1977-3/1/1978 (Box 46, Folder 654)
  - Personnel: Field Stat and Director Search, 1/6/1980-3/23/1981 (Box 46, Folder 655)
  - Personnel: Friedman, Jill A., 6/26/1979-5/24/1983 (Box 46, Folder 656)
  - Personnel: Leary, Eilleen, 3/27/1978-6/25/1985 (Box 46, Folder 657)
  - Personnel: Shu, David S. K., 8/10/1980-2/24/1981 (Box 46, Folder 658)
  - Personnel: Simpson, Jan A., 3/14/1988-5/4/1988 (Box 46, Folder 659)
  - Personnel: Teason, Donald P., 8/8/1981-6/23/1987 (Box 46, Folder 660)
  - Personnel: Thomas, Mildred D., 10/23/1973-9/1/1982 (Box 46, Folder 661)
  - Personnel: Walko, Ann A., 5/1/1973-9/23/1977 (Box 46, Folder 662)
  - Perspectives on Contemporary China: 1980-1981 Lecture Series, 6/26/1980-7/30/1981 (Box 46, Folder 663)
  - Pettus Family, 1/18/1963-11/3/1977 (Box 46, Folder 664)
  - Pinney, Edward S. (Trustee), 4/16/1975-3/20/1978 (Box 47, Folder 665)
  - Poetry Lecture: Huang, 1972-12/21/1973 (Box 47, Folder 666)
  - Portfolio Project, 1966-2/1977 (Box 47, Folder 667)
  - Powell, Mrs. Maude, 10/19/1979-3/4/1986 (Box 47, Folder 668)
  - Princeton in Asia, 10/2/1967-2/17/1976 (Box 47, Folder 669)
  - Program Expenses and Income, 3/1974-10/14/1974 (Box 47, Folder 670)
  - Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 671)
  - Programs: Holdridge Lecture, 8/25/1981-2/26/1982 (Box 47, Folder 672)
  - Programs: Medical Symposium, 6/1985 (Box 47, Folder 673)
  - Programs: Reception and Dinner at China Institute, 4/2/1979-6/24/1982 (Box 47, Folder 674)
  - Programs: Gordon Ross Taping Visit, 9/1983 (Box 47, Folder 675)
  - Programs: Yu Shyying Lecture Demo., 4/1/1981-4/19/1982 (Box 47, Folder 676)
  - Programs: Spence Bookwarming, 10/26/1984 (Box 47, Folder 677)
  - Programs: Yale Club of Philadelphia, 5/30/1984 (Box 47, Folder 678)
  - Programs: Yale Clubs of Wyoming and Colorado, 4/22/1985-5/2/1985 (Box 47, Folder 679)
  - Programs: Thomas Wiens Dinner/Lecture, 11/18/1977-12/6/1977 (Box 47, Folder 680)
  - Projects Meeting, 4/1978 (Box 47, Folder 681)
  - Projects: Nanking Univ, PRC, 5/31/1973-7/3/1974 (Box 47, Folder 682)
  - Proposed Programs for 1975-1976, 3/18/1975-9/3/1975 (Box 47, Folder 683)
  - Proposed Trip to the PRC, 7/24/1974-2/16/1979 (Box 47, Folder 684)
  - Publicity, 3/1974-1/13/1975 (Box 47, Folder 685)
  - Publicity (I), 2/1/1974-10/6/1974 (Box 47, Folder 686)
  - Publicity (II), 10/8/1973-2/5/1978 (Box 47, Folder 687)
  - Publicity, 1975-1982 (Box 47, Folder 688)
  - Publicity: Chinese Dinner Drama, 3/19/1974-3/30/1974 (Box 48, Folder 689)
  - Publicity: China in Yale, 2/3/1974-10/6/1974 (Box 48, Folder 690)
  - Publicity: Cities, List, Speakers, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 691)
  - Publicity: Costs, Appeal Folders, Annual Report, 1971-10/9/1974 (Box 48, Folder 692)
  - Publicity: External, 1/16/1974-11/8/1976 (Box 48, Folder 693)
  - Publicity: Follow-Ups and Appeal Letters, 9/1961-9/13/1973 (Box 48, Folder 694)
  - Publicity: Outside, 10/16/1974-6/11/1975 (Box 48, Folder 695)
  - Publicity: Newsletters, 1965-1973 (Box 48, Folder 696)
  - Publicity: Newspaper Clippings, 12/20/1973-10/22/1977 (Box 48, Folder 697)
  - Publicity: Release Lists, Poster Lists, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 698)
  - Publicity: Schedule, Proposed Budget, Design Items, 3/9/1974-12/3/1976 (Box 48, Folder 699)
  - "R", 11/28/1972-6/13/1979 (Box 48, Folder 700)
  - Reception Invitations, 10/1973 (Box 48, Folder 701)
  - Remington, Nancy Roth, 3/3/1975-10/17/1977 (Box 48, Folder 702)
  - Remington, Nancy Roth: Budget, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 703)
  - Reports to the Trustees, 11/13/1960-6/4/1973 (Box 48, Folder 704)
  - Reports from Hong Kong, 9/28/1958-4/9/1959 (Box 48, Folder 705)
  - Report of the Executive Secretary to the Trustees, 7/7/1955-6/28/1958, 10/27/1955-4/24/1956 (Box 48, Folder 706-707)
  - Representative Job Details, 2/1/1974-4/20/1974 (Box 48, Folder 708)
  - Representative Selection Committee, 3/7/1974-3/15/1974 (Box 48, Folder 709)
  - Resolution Y-I-C, New Asia College and Chinese Univ. of H. K. Relationship Passed by Y & C Trustees, 12/11/1966 (Box 48, Folder 710)
  - Rockefeller, Godfrey S., 12/20/1972-1/25/1982 (Box 48, Folder 711)
  - Rugh, Dwight, 4/29/1980-3/29/1981 (Box 48, Folder 712)
  - "S", 9/8/1972-10/13/1978 (Box 48, Folder 713)
  - Salem Trip 9/13/1979 (Box 48, Folder 714)
  - Scholarships, Tuition: Letters, Donors and Recipients, 5/22/1972-1/4/1979 (Box 48, Folder 715)
  - Scholarships, Tuition: For Students in New Asia College, 1968-12/1972 (Box 49, Folder 716)
  - Scholarships, Tuition: Lists of Donors, Correspondence, 1971-4/13/1973, 1969-1/17/1970, 1968-6/5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 717-719)
  - Scholarships, Tuition: Recipients' "Thank You" Notes Received, 3/4/1967-4/1/1969 (Box 49, Folder 720)
  - Schoyer, B. P.: Biographical Sketch and Personal, 3/20/1952-3/23/1978 (Box 49, Folder 721)
  - Schoyer, B. P.: Official Correspondence, 7/28/1967-3/1978 (Box 49, Folder 722)
  - Schoyer, B. P.: Hong Kong Trip, 12/1/1972-6/1/1976 (Box 49, Folder 723)
  - Schoyer, B. P.: Memorial Fund (1 of 2), 11/3/1972-4/1913/1978 (Box 49, Folder 724)
  - Schoyer, B. P.: Memorial Fund (2 of 2), 4/13/1978-10/1925/1984 (Box 49, Folder 725)
  - Schoyer, B. P.: Speaking Engagements, 2/28/1973-3/9/1977 (Box 49, Folder 726)
  - Schoyer, B. P.: Speeches, 3/15/1973-10/10/1977 (Box 49, Folder 727)
  - Scirpo, Tracy (Personnel), 8/10/1987-12/23/1987 (Box 49, Folder 728)
  - September Members' Meeting, 1915-6/16/1916 (Box 49, Folder 729)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Celebration, 9/1967-2/1971 (Box 49, Folder 730)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Celebration: Fund ($70,000) (1 of 2), 12/1970-5/1971 (Box 49, Folder 731)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Celebration: Fund ($70,000) (2 of 2), 6/1971-4/1972 (Box 50, Folder 732)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Celebration: Dinner, Presidents' Room, Woolsey Hall, 1/1971-2/1971 (Box 50, Folder 733)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Celebration: Committee-Lovett, Arnold, Cochran, 11/1970-5/1971 (Box 50, Folder 734)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Celebration: Lists used to Solicit Funds for 70th Anniversary, 3/1971-9/1971 (Box 50, Folder 735)
  - Seventieth Anniversary Celebration: Lists of Invited Persons and Acceptances, 1/1971-6/1971 (Box 50, Folder 736)